

WEB DEVELOPER + SEO

Details

B7-1530B 20th Street
Brandon, R7B2M6
Canada
2049221305
hirenpatel6777@gmail.com

15/03/1992

Links

LinkedIn

Skills

HTML5

CSS3

Bootstrap 4

Java Script

jQuery

AJAX

Angular JS

XML

Git

Wordpress

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Social Media Marketing

Google Analytics

Google Search Console

On Page SEO

Profile

Over 5+ years experience in IT industry specifically in UI/UX Designer. a Bachelor of Engineering degree in computer science. Top-notch communication and multitasking skills with a proactive mentality and flexible approach to problem solving. Goal-oriented and proficient team player motivated to increase abilities and make a positive impact on team projects.

Employment History

Web Developer + SEO, PBC Multi Media, Brandon, MB, Canada

DECEMBER 2020 - PRESENT

- Conceptualizing creative ideas with clients.
- Followed policies and procedures related to application methods and quality standards at all times.
- Remained knowledgeable in new standards, technologies, and trends in website development.
- Incorporating functionalities and features into websites.
- Maintaining the appearance of websites by enforcing content standards.
- Designing visual imagery for websites and ensuring that they are in line with branding for clients.
- Effetively multitasked and worked well with internal and external teams.

Web Designer, Sanah Infosolutions Pvt.Ltd., Vadodara, India

AUGUST 2017 - FEBRUARY 2020

- Remained dedicated to emerging technology and the latest digital marketing concepts.
- Created detaisl technical and user documentation.
- Designing sample pages including colors and fonts.
- Preparing design plans and presenting the website structure.
- Testing and improving the design of the website.
- Establishing design guidelines, standards, and best practices.
- Maintaining the appearance of websites by enforcing content standards

Web Designer, PriyaSharm Software Pvt. Ltd., Vadodara, India

AUGUST 2016 - AUGUST 2017

- Testing and improving the design of the website.
- Maintaining the appearance of websites by enforcing content standards.
- Email blast design using photo shop.

Web Designer, LenDen Club(Innofin Solutions Private Limited), Mumbai, India.

JULY 2015 - JULY 2016

- Maintaining the appearance of websites by enforcing content standards.
- Testing and improving the design of the website.

Education

Bachelor of engineering (Computer Science), R.R Institution Of Technology (VTU), Bangalore- India

AUGUST 2009 - MAY 2013

Soft Skills

Team player, Self-learner, Advanced problem-solver, Innovative, Creative, Good Communication

SEMrush Screaming Frog Hobbies Music Travelling Reading Languages English Hindi Gujarati

Operating Systems

Windows 11/10/8/7/XP, Linux, Mac OS

Extra-curricular activities

Volunteering

- Active Member Of BAPS Youth Club.
- Leader in Ozone event Organized by RRIT college.

References

References available upon request